<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="${descVersion}">
	<author>${author}</author>
	<version>${version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>${title}</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
As the name implies, progressive steering is based on a progressive steering ratio.
This significantly increase the precision in high-speed maneuvering.
On twisting roads and at junctions, the driver will notice a more dynamic response as a result of the more direct steering.
This mod is especially aimed for gamepads and medium to low degrees steering-wheels, you can change the settings to better fit your hardware and driving style by pressing "RSHIFT + R".
On multiplayer everyone will have it's own custom settings.
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Wie der Name schon sagt, basiert die Progressivlenkung auf einer progressiven Lenkübersetzung.
Dadurch wird die Präzision beim Manövrieren bei hohen Geschwindigkeiten deutlich erhöht.
Auf kurvigen Straßen und an Kreuzungen wird der Fahrer durch die direktere Lenkung ein dynamischeres Ansprechverhalten bemerken.
Dieser Mod ist speziell für Gamepads und Lenkräder mit mittlerem bis niedrigem Lenkeinschlag gedacht. Sie können die Einstellungen mit "RSHIFT + R" an Ihre Hardware und Ihren Fahrstil anpassen.
Im Multiplayer wird jeder seine eigenen Einstellungen haben.
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Comme son nom l'indique, le pilotage progressif est basé sur un rapport de pilotage progressif.
Cela augmente considérablement la précision des manœuvres à grande vitesse.
Sur les routes sinueuses et aux carrefours, le conducteur constatera une réponse plus dynamique grâce à la direction plus directe.
Ce mode est spécialement conçu pour les manettes de jeu et les volants à moyen et bas degrés. Vous pouvez modifier les réglages pour mieux adapter votre matériel et votre style de conduite en appuyant sur "RSHIFT + R".
En mode multijoueur, chacun aura ses propres paramètres personnalisés.
]]>
		</fr>
	</description>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="rmod/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="utility/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="rset/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="progressiveSteering.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n>
		<text name="ps_mod_settings_title">
			<en>Progressive Steering Settings</en>
			<de>Progressive Steering einstellungen</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision">
			<en>Precision</en>
			<de>Genauigkeit</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_1">
			<en>Low</en>
			<de>Niedrig</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_2">
			<en>Medium</en>
			<de>Mittel</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_3">
			<en>High</en>
			<de>Hoch</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_4">
			<en>Very High</en>
			<de>Sehr hoch</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_5">
			<en>Partial</en>
			<de>Teilweise</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_6">
			<en>Smooth</en>
			<de>Glatt</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_tooltip">
			<en>Choose the precision that better fit with your hardware and driving style.</en>
			<de>Wählen Sie die Präzision, die besser mit Ihrer Hardware und Ihrem Fahrstil passt.</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_enabled">
			<en>Enabled</en>
			<de>Aktiviert</de>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_enabled_tooltip">
			<en>Enable / Disable progressive steering.</en>
			<de>Aktivieren / Deaktivieren Der Progressive Steering.</de>
		</text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
