<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="${descVersion}">
	<author>${author}</author>
	<version>${version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>${title}</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
As the name implies, progressive steering is based on a progressive steering ratio.
This significantly increase the precision in high-speed maneuvering.
On twisting roads and at junctions, the driver will notice a more dynamic response as a result of the more direct steering.
This mod is especially aimed for gamepads and medium to low degrees steering-wheels, you can change the settings to better fit your hardware and driving style by pressing "RSHIFT + R".
On multiplayer everyone will have it's own custom settings.

Changelog ${version}:
- Added new translations
- Added adaptive steering (increase control at high speeds)
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Wie der Name schon sagt, basiert die Progressivlenkung auf einer progressiven Lenkübersetzung.
Dadurch wird die Präzision beim Manövrieren bei hohen Geschwindigkeiten deutlich erhöht.
Auf kurvigen Straßen und an Kreuzungen wird der Fahrer durch die direktere Lenkung ein dynamischeres Ansprechverhalten bemerken.
Dieser Mod ist speziell für Gamepads und Lenkräder mit mittlerem bis niedrigem Lenkeinschlag gedacht. Sie können die Einstellungen mit "RSHIFT + R" an Ihre Hardware und Ihren Fahrstil anpassen.
Im Multiplayer wird jeder seine eigenen Einstellungen haben.

Changelog ${version}:
- Neue Übersetzungen hinzugefügt
- Adaptive Lenkung hinzugefügt (Kontrolle bei hohen Geschwindigkeiten erhöhen)
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Comme son nom l'indique, le pilotage progressif est basé sur uen direction plus progressive et asservie à votre vitesse.
Cela augmente considérablement la précision des manœuvres à grande vitesse.
Sur les routes sinueuses et aux carrefours, le conducteur constatera une réponse plus dynamique grâce à la direction plus directe.
Ce mod est spécialement conçu pour les manettes de jeu et les volants à degrés de rotation réduits. Vous pouvez modifier les réglages pour mieux adapter votre matériel et votre style de conduite en appuyant sur "RSHIFT + R".
En mode multijoueur, chacun aura ses propres paramètres personnalisés.

Changelog ${version}:
- Ajout de nouvelles traductions
- Direction adaptative ajoutée (augmentation du contrôle à haute vitesse)
]]>
		</fr>
	</description>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="rmod/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="utility/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="rset/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="progressiveSteering.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n>
		<text name="ps_mod_settings_title">
			<en>Progressive Steering Settings</en>
			<fr>Paramètres de la direction progressive</fr>
			<de>Progressive Steering einstellungen</de>
			<pl>Ustawienia Progressive Steering</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision">
			<en>Precision</en>
			<fr>Précision</fr>
			<de>Genauigkeit</de>
			<pl>Precyzja</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_1">
			<en>Low</en>
			<fr>Basse</fr>
			<de>Niedrig</de>
			<pl>Niska</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_2">
			<en>Medium</en>
			<fr>Moyenne</fr>
			<de>Mittel</de>
			<pl>Średnia</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_3">
			<en>High</en>
			<fr>Haute</fr>
			<de>Hoch</de>
			<pl>Wysoka</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_4">
			<en>Very High</en>
			<fr>Très haute</fr>
			<de>Sehr hoch</de>
			<pl>Bardzo wysoka</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_5">
			<en>Partial</en>
			<fr>Partielle</fr>
			<de>Teilweise</de>
			<pl>Częściowa</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_6">
			<en>Smooth</en>
			<fr>Linéaire</fr>
			<de>Glatt</de>
			<pl>Gładka</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_precision_tooltip">
			<en>Choose the precision that better fit with your hardware and driving style.</en>
			<fr>Choisissez votre précision qui s'adapte le mieux à votre équipement et votre style de conduite</fr>
			<de>Wählen Sie die Präzision, die besser mit Ihrer Hardware und Ihrem Fahrstil passt.</de>
			<pl>Wybierz precyzję, która najlepiej lepiej pasuje do Twojego sprzętu i stylu jazdy.</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_enabled">
			<en>Enabled</en>
			<fr>Activée</fr>
			<de>Aktiviert</de>
			<pl>Włączona</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_enabled_tooltip">
			<en>Enable / Disable progressive steering.</en>
			<fr>Active / Désactive la direction progressive</fr>
			<de>Aktivieren / Deaktivieren Der Progressive Steering.</de>
			<pl>Włącz/Wyłącz Progressive Steering</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_a_enabled">
			<en>Adaptive Steering</en>
			<fr>Direction progressive</fr>
			<de>Adaptive Lenkung</de>
			<pl>Sterowania adaptacyjne</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="ps_setting_a_enabled_tooltip">
			<en>Enable / Disable adaptive steering (increase control at high speeds).</en>
			<fr>Active / Désactive la direction progressive (meilleur contrôle à grande vitesse)</fr>
			<de>Aktivieren / Deaktivieren der adaptiven Lenkung (Erhöhung der Kontrolle bei hohen Geschwindigkeiten).</de>
			<pl>Włącza/Wyłącza sterowania adaptacyjne (zwiększona kntrola przy wyższej prędkości).</pl>
		</text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
